http://www.pollen.com/help/privacy

No locations found
Help us improve our mobile app.
Take a quick survey here.
x
Advert
Your trust and privacy is of the greatest importance to Pollen.com
We are committed to protecting the online privacy of our visitors' personally identifiable information. To better protect your privacy online, this statement explains our online information practices at this Web-site.
Privacy Statement
Pollen.com is the leading provider of allergy forecast information on the internet. Our goal is to offer you accurate and timely information to help you manage your allergies, and to provide you with access to the most useful personal allergy information available, through the innovative use of today's latest technology.
Because Pollen.com takes your privacy very seriously, our website employs security measures designed to protect you. We do not share or sell your personal information, including your email address, with other companies for any reason, except as required by law or as described in this Privacy statement, unless you have given us specific permission to do so.
1. What personally identifiable information do we gather?
There are several places on our website where we collect information from you, for example on the Allergy Alert™ registration page; when you answer some questions on the Compare Yourself quiz; when you answer the Allergy Quiz.
We may collect the following types of personally identifiable information at this Web-site: name, zip code, e-mail and telephone number. We also may collect other information such as an IP address that may be personally identifiable in some situations.
We use this information to provide you information through our site and our applications, to respond to your requests, which include providing you with our product and service updates, to enable you to participate in surveys or questionnaires posted on our site, and to provide you with opportunities to learn about other products, programs, or services that we believe may be of interest to you. Generally speaking, we do not share personally identifiable information with unrelated third parties who are not covered by this privacy statement without your prior permission.
2. Non-Personally Identifiable Information
To enhance your experience at Pollen.com, with our site, we may use “cookies” or other tagging mechanisms to track your visit to our website.
Cookies are text files that may be stored in your computer's browser (i.e. in memory for the duration of the active session) or on the user's hard drive by the software we use on our network of sites to store your preferences and perform other administrative functions. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the user experience, create personalized offerings, and improve the content and offerings on our network of sites. Some of our software vendors use cookies for purposes that may be different from those stated in our Privacy Statement, and our Privacy Statement does not cover our software vendors' collection and use of your information by way of cookies in connection with our site.
Our site does not currently respond to Do Not Track requests.
If you have questions about tracking practices on this site, please contact us through the means described below.
We may collect additional non-personally identifiable information using other tagging mechanisms about our visitors when you visit many of our Web pages, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows or OS X), the domain name of your Internet service provider and other browser collected information, including browser add-ons, geolocation, and mobile geolocation, (to the extent you allow it).
3. How do we use your information?
We have three main uses for your information: tracking your visit at Pollen.com, providing you with our Allergy Alert™ e-mail service, and being able to contact you (a) at your request, or,
(b) because you have authorized us to share your information with our marketing partners for special offers which may be of interest to you.
We track your visit at Pollen.com with the information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to better personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage.
E-mail addresses supplied for Pollen.com's Allergy Alert™ Newsletter are also private and used only for the newsletter's distribution list. If you currently receive our newsletter and would like to 'unsubscribe,' simply follow the directions at the bottom of one of our mailings in the "Unsubscribe" section.
We occasionally send e-mail and promotional notifications to users of our site.
We may also engage third-party vendors to act on our behalf and administer our e-mail services, which would require disclosure of the e-mail address you provided to us to such vendors, acting on our instructions. We may use this information in the aggregate to analyze the effectiveness of our e-mail and promotional notifications and site usage, either by us, or through our third-party e-mail provider. If you wish to discontinue receipt of e-mail or promotional notifications from us, please email unsubscribe@pollen.com, or follow the “unsubscribe” instructions at the end of the e-mail or promotional notification.
4. With whom will your information be shared?
We do not share or sell your personal information, including your email address, with other companies for any reason, except as provided in this Privacy Statement or as required by law.
We may disclose information we maintain in response to legal proceedings, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company.
5. Delete/Deactivate Policy
If you would like your information to be deleted or deactivated from our site, please contact us by e-mail using the contact information near the bottom of this statement.
6. Security Standards
We have appropriate security measures in place to prevent unauthorized access to the information that we collect online.
We have implemented various security features to help protect your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Despite these measures, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized persons will always be unable to defeat our security measures. Accordingly, we are not responsible for the security or confidentiality of information transmitted or accessible via the Internet.
In addition, we use virus protection software, and also maintain policies or practices designed to limit access to your personal information to employees who need access in order to carry out their job responsibilities.
7. Links
Several sections of our website offer links to other websites we believe you may be interested in.
Although we make every effort to select sites that we feel might be of interest to you, we cannot guarantee your privacy when visiting one of these sites, and these practices may be different than ours.
Remember - these sites are not related to us; we provide these links as a courtesy to you. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties, and our Privacy Statement does not cover activities occurring at other Web sites.
8. Terms of Use
This Privacy Statement is part of, and subject to, the Terms and Conditions applicable to products, services and activities available through www.pollen.com.
Third Party Entities
Third party entities, including Google, use cookies to serve ads on our web site based on a user's prior visits to the website (or, potentially, to other web sites). Google's use of these cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visits to this and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of these cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings (alternatively, users can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting aboutads.info).
Questions
Questions regarding our privacy practices or this statement should be directed to:
Pollen.com
c/o IQVIA
1 IMS Drive
Plymouth Meeting, PA 19462
Send us a message by clicking here.
Advertisement
Advert
